sandlotgames.com 2011-06-07

# SANDLOT GAMES PRIVACY POLICY

Sandlot Games takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. By visiting Sandlot Games, or accessing any Sandlot Service you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy, and the Sandlot Games Terms of Service.

**Information Collected**

Sandlot may collect the following information if you visit our website, use any Sandlot Service as referenced in the Terms of Service, register to play our games, or register to receive our newsletter:

  * Username
  * Email Address, Password, and IP Address
  * Date of birth
  * Gender
  * Locale(country and language)
  * Social Network User Identifiers including, first, last, and usernames
  * Payment Information (credit card, debit, pay pal)

**Use of Collected Information**

Information collected may be used to e-mail you with messages about our services or third party products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. These messages may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the messages, including whether the email was opened and/or what links (if any) were clicked. We use your username, e-mail address, and password to uniquely identify you as a user on the Sandlot Games web site. We may use or display your username for the purposes of rankings, competitions, chat identification, and/or game high scores. If you participate in our "Share a Level" or “Submit a Level” feature, your e-mail and IP addresses will be shared with Sandlot and the person to whom you send a level to using this feature. We may also use an IP address to exercise our ability to restrict access to the site by users who have violated our Terms of Service, detect and report fraud Your contact information will allow us to notify you about new features, enhancements, resolution of site problems, handle and/or route your customer support questions and issues, and inform you of upgrade opportunities, contests, prizes, and/or special events. We do not share your username, password, IP address, date of birth, gender, locale, personally-identifiable statistical and usage data, or social network user identifiers with any third party.

**Credit Cards**

Sandlot Games reveals only the user name, address, and the last four digits of your credit card number when confirming an order. We then transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. Sandlot does not maintain end user credit card information on its data bases. 

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

**Security of Collected Information**

Sandlot Games takes reasonable steps to protect the privacy of your data. All data that we collect is stored off-site on secure databases. The only access to this data is by Sandlot employees who have a need to know in carrying out their job functions within the organization. All Sandlot employees are bound to a nondisclosure agreement that legally restricts the disclosure of company and customer information. 

**Statistical and Usage Data**

If you choose to participate in helping us focus test our games, then we may retrieve information about your hardware system and how your game is used. We use this information to enable you to play your game over the internet. We also use this information to better understand the behavior and preferences of our customers, so we can improve our products and services. 

**Links to Third Party Sites**

Web sites that link to or from a Sandlot Games web site may collect personal information about you. This Sandlot Games Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, other web sites.

**Chat and Messaging**

Sandlot Games may operate message boards and/or chat areas where users can exchange ideas and communicate with each another. When posting to a message board or chat area, the information is being made publicly available in an online environment. Any information posted is the sole responsibility of the individual user.

**Children**

The Sandlot Games web site is not directed to children under the age of 13\. Sandlot Games respects the privacy of parents and children and is committed to complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). When registering, Sandlot Games does not collect personal information from individuals who identify themselves as under the age of 13. If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to Sandlot Games, he or she can contact us at [support@sandlotgames.com](mailto:support@sandlotgames.com) . Sandlot Games will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13. 

**Security**

Sandlot Games has taken reasonable steps to protect the security of your information by following industry standards developed by industry leaders for the ongoing development, enhancement, storage, dissemination and implementation of security standards for account data protection. 

**Agreement with Sandlot Games Policies**

By using any of the Sandlot Games websites, products or services, you signify your understanding of and agreement with this Privacy Policy, and to our Terms of Service. If you do not agree with our policies, please do not use any of the Sandlot Games web sites, products, or services.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

Sandlot Games reserves the right to change this privacy policy without notice. Therefore, please check back periodically for any changes.

**Contact Us**

To contact us with questions or complaints regarding privacy, please contact us at [privacy@sandlotgames.com](mailto:privacy@sandlotgames.com) or write to us at Sandlot Games Legal Department. 22118 20th Avenue SE, Suite 130, Bothell, WA 98021.
